ready
go start
recording all right so I want to do a
quick video from my wife's office in the
bell tower at the mall
center uh as luck would have it we
walked down here after getting the
Subaru worked on
so she give me a ride and we did a we
had a fun ride on the lime scooter it
was really
great
and there's been some questions about
how the pocket 3 deals with Focus so I
just wanted to show you a little bit so
right now and I don't even know if it's
actually focused on me properly or maybe
it's focused on the corner of the table
but right now the pocket 3 is in the
middle setting which is called
continuous and what that does is it it
Focus is cinematically on a very small
field that's like up close but it's
really highly focused and it it gives
that whole cinematic effect and I'm
going to show you so my wife gave me a
gave me
a my wife gave me a Selzer right so it
like cinematically it'll focus on the
closest thing to it and then and you you
as you plan out it it focuses on ever
and if you're if your bike streaming
goes without saying that you you don't
want that mode if you've got handlebars
in front of you if you got a chest Mount
like I've been wearing all day my
shirt's a little wet then you know you
don't want that unless you're going to
be stopping all the time so like you
know like we we went we went into
Victoria's Secret with the pink panties
remember and you know if you hold the
panties up close you get to see those up
really close and it blurs out everything
in the back so that's just that's what
that is it's called um continuous U and
I accidentally leave it in single which
is the first setting and single actually
locks down a specific distance and I use
single anytime in the car when I need to
make it focus on something that's not
the windshield or when it's on my chest
that I need to make it focus on
something that's not the handlebars
right um and this is actually one of the
downsides of the pocket 3 is if if like
if you're doing something like like for
mountain biking uh the pocket 3 really
is kind of bad because it doesn't give
first of all the wide field of view is a
different thing but but it you know you
can actually have the the handlebars be
in Focus as well as everything in front
of you because you have infinite focus
with the action four as opposed to the
pocket 3 the pocket 3 doesn't have that
the pocket 3 has single mode which which
you can lock down to something far away
and then your handlebars will always be
blurry right uh but and then the problem
with that is if you forget which I I
just did that's what prompted this video
is that they can't they can't see
anything because you know it's like oh
your your camera's got problems with
focus and there's a third vers there's a
third setting which I almost never use
and it's called
Product uh what is it product showcase I
think it is and what it does is it it it
favors anything in the foreground
anything so so like right
now I'm hoping that it's focusing on me
even though there's something else
closer in the foreground right it it's
when you're going to continue mode it's
usually intelligent about picking out
the right thing but when you're in
product showcase mode it locks down on
whatever the closest thing is as fast as
possible so it's really great if you're
like zooming in on the hardware and
electronics I haven't done a lot of
those shots yet but when you're like
trying to shoot really close um and show
all the detail on your raspberry Kay or
your soldering or your jewelry making or
whatever uh or that